<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Approximate Knowledge</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Approximate Knowledge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Figures</title>
      <link>/post/figures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/figures/</guid>
      <description>Some figures are given with no caption. In this case, take them as art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words</title>
      <link>/post/words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/words/</guid>
      <description>Use words for brevity and clarity. This blog does not accept liability for any damages incurred via the misuse of words.
Contradistinction  The difference between two or more things that is made clear by comparing them:
 I use the term &amp;ldquo;child&amp;rdquo; in contradistinction to &amp;ldquo;parent&amp;rdquo; - it does not necessarily refer to a juvenile. - Cambridge
 Inferential role semantics is an approach to the theory of meaning that identifies the meaning of an expression with its relationship to other expressions, in contradistinction to denotationalism, according to which denotations are the primary sort of meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>/post/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/quotes/</guid>
      <description>Quotes can lose their intended meaning when taken out of context. If you like something here, then follow it up via the links.
 &amp;ldquo;Practicing diplomats and politicians have often found their margin of success depends on their ability to seize upon unique twists in the political or psychological environment, twists which allow the individual to escape the seemingly uncontrollable tide of events that one would expect a mathematical model to extrapolate&amp;hellip; one achieves a greater &amp;lsquo;benefit&amp;rsquo; within a given &amp;lsquo;cost-constraint,&amp;rsquo; not by being tight and precise about budgeting one&amp;rsquo;s resources, but rather by preserving the detachment and freedom one will need in order to seize upon whole new options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>